Finding Aid for F. George Robins papers, 1915-1919.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
F. George Robins papers 1915-1919
Robins, F. George.
0.2 linear feet
Soldier from Port Huron, Mich., member of Co. B, 339th U.S. Infantry who served in the Allied intervention in Russia, 1918-1920, the "Polar Bear Expedition." Collection includes letters describing primarily food and the weather.
87222 Aa 1
Bentley Historical Library University of Michigan
The collection was donated by Donald H. Cleeves, of Lansing, Michigan, in 1987 (Donor no.: 7449 ), and by Frederick G. Bruso, of Laingsburg, Michigan, in 2008 (Donor no.: 10143 ).
The collection is open for research.
Resident of Port Huron, Mich., served as corporal and sergeant, Co. B, 339th Infantry.
Letters describing daily activities; also diaries containing brief descriptions of his activities in Russia and of his passage home. Most of the collection has not been digitized.
Subjects
Robins, F. George.; Soviet Union--History--Allied Intervention, 1918-1920.; World War, 1914-1918.; Polar Bear Expedition.
- Papers
  - Letters1918-1919, 4 items (Folder 1)
    Digital copies available.
  - Diaries1918-1919, 2 items (Folder 2)
  - Correspondence
    - Empty envelopes and undated (Folder 3)
    - 1915-1917 (Folder 4)
    - 1918 Jan.-May (Folder 5)
    - 1918 June-July (Folder 6)
    - 1918 Aug.-Sept. (Folder 7)
    - 1918 Oct.-Dec. (Folder 8)
    - 1919 (Folder 9)
- Photographs
  - Photographs (Folder 10)